{
    "subject": "resource/Rize_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Documentary_films_about_African_Americans",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the film Rize is documentary films about African Americans.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7781097888946533,
            "question": "What is the subject of the film 'Rize'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7514463067054749,
            "question": "What themes might a documentary about African Americans explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7034255266189575,
            "question": "Which group of people are documentary films about in 'Rize' focused on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5315002202987671,
            "question": "What kind of films are documentaries about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3249721825122833,
            "question": "Why do you think documentaries like 'Rize' are important?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2540312707424164,
            "question": "What are some challenges filmmakers might face when creating documentaries about sensitive topics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2146124243736267,
            "question": "Is 'Rize' a fictional story or a real-life depiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18733876943588257,
            "question": "What elements make a good documentary film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1564604938030243,
            "question": "How can documentaries influence people's understanding of the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11297888308763504,
            "question": "Can you name other documentaries that focus on specific communities or cultures?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the film Rize is documentary films about African Americans.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3719_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can documentaries influence people's understanding of the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3719_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What elements make a good documentary film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3719_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Rize' a fictional story or a real-life depiction?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3719_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3719_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3719_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3719_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3719_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3719_152.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3719_158.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3719_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3719_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3719_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3719_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents provide information about a documentary film called \"Rize\" that focuses on the lives of Black Americans in South Central Los Angeles, and the struggles they go through. The film also introduces two types of dancing groups: Clowning and Krumping, which are both associated with African American culture. Therefore, the subject of the film Rize can be considered as documentary films about African Americans."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The subject of the film Rize is documentary films about African Americans.\" The documents describe Rize as a documentary focusing on the lives of Black Americans in South Central Los Angeles, their struggles, and the dance cultures like clowning and krumping."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}